Guide to the The Exit Art Archive 1982 - 2011 MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings Mexico, January - May 1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings North Africa, January - May 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings Pacific Islands, 1986, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings Philippines, May 8, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings Poland, May 4, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings Puerto Rico, May 8, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings Spain, 1987 - 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings Switzerland, January - March 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings United Kingdom, May 11, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings United States, May 6, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings Venezuela, May 5, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: International Screenings West Germany, May 3, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Research Materials - Film/Video Festivals, Programs, Exhibitions, Related Organizations [1 of 4], 1986 - 1988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Research Materials - Film/Video Festivals, Programs, Exhibitions, Related Organizations [2 of 4], 1986 - 1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Research Materials - Film/Video Festivals, Programs, Exhibitions, Related Organizations [3 of 4], 1986 - 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Research Materials - Film/Video Festivals, Programs, Exhibitions, Related Organizations [4 of 4], 1986 - 1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Research Materials - Media, Press (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Public Programs - Workshop Super 8 Film to Video (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Public Programs - Workshop Intro to Sync Sound Filmmaking (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Public Programs - Workshop Super 8 for Broadcast, March 21, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Public Programs - Roundtable Discussions Flyer, May 14 - 15, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Public Programs - Workshop Super 8 to Video The Documentary Form, May 9, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Publication "Foreign Correspondence - The International Super 8 Phenomenon", 1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Expenses / Receipts (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Visitor Sign-In Log (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Press Clippings and Advertisements (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Catalog Essays (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - International Forum of Super 8 [1988.06]: Catalog Orders (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Invitation Letter to Artists, February 12, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artist Rejection Letters, February 18, 1988; February 26, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Research Materials (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Invitations, June 4, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Press Release, June 4, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: List of Embassies, June 1988 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: List of Artists (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Exhibition Checklist, June 4, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Shipping Information (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Rudolph Baranik, March 7, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Betty Beaumont (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Luis Camnitzer (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Jaime Davidovich (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Juan Downey, February - March 1988 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Leon Ferrari, 1987 - 1988 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Ilona Granet (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Cildo Miereles (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Catalina Parra (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Christy Rupp (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - John Strauss (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Marta Minujin (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artists - Regina Vater [With Slides] (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Artist's Thank You Letter - Richard Armijo, September 20, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Visitor Sign-In Log, June 4 - 30, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Press Clippings, June - July 1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - The Debt [1988.07]: Catalogue Requests (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Possible Titles, 1986 - 1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Invitations / Mailers, September 17, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Biographical Information, Press Pack, 1988, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Contracts, April 15, 1988; August 23, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Budget (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Correspondence, 1986 - 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Loan Information, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Shipping Information (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Exhibition Checklist, September 17, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Stencils (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Invite List, Invitations, Dinner Party, October 26, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Press Clippings, 1988 - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Exhibition Travel - Cleveland State University, February 10 - March 17, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Catalogue Text (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Price List, September 17, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Anton van Dalen: The Memory Cabinet [1988.08]: Catalogue Orders, [October 1988] (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Invitations, November 5, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Press Release, November 5, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Contract, April 15, 1988; August 23, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Biographical Information (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Correspondence, 1988 - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Loan Information, November - December 1988 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Shipping Information, 1988 - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Exhibition Checklist, November 5, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Price List, 1988, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Press Clippings, 1988 - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Martin Wong [1988.09]: Catalogue Text, 1988, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Invitations, January 14, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Press Release, January 14, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Contract, December 13, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Biographical Information, [1988] (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Correspondence, September 11, 1989; September 19, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Shipping Information (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Exhibition Checklist, January 14, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Price List, January 14, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Press Clipping - Eileen Myles for Art in America, September 1989 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Sonia Balassanian [1989.01]: Catalogue Essay, "The Art of Brooding" by Donald Kuspit (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Invitations, February 18, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Press Release, February 18, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Contract, December 7, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Correspondence, 1989, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Loan Information, 1988 - 1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Artist's Statement, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Exhibition Checklist, February 18, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Price List, February 18, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Press Clippings (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Catalogue Text and Artist Resume (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Jane Hammond [1989.02]: Catalogue Printing Information (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Invitations, April 8, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Press Release, April 8, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Biographical Information (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Artist's Statement, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Exhibition Checklist and Floor Plan (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Price List (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Press Clipping [Bijutsu Techo Cover Photocopy], July 1989 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Hiroshi Kariya: Sutra [1989.03]: Exhibition Travel - Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania, March 10 - April 25, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Invitations, May 13, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Contract, April 15, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Biographical Information (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Correspondence, 1985 - 1990 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Clients / Reserves (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Accounting - Sales and Loans, 1989 - 1991 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Public Programs - Incubration (Poetry / Fiction Reading), June 1, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Press Clippings (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Catalogue - Getty Grant, 1989 - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Catalogue - "David Hammons: Soldier in the Army of Harlem's History" by Robert Farris Thompson, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Catalogue - Greg Tate Essay, December 1990 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Catalogue - Interview by J. Ingberman and P. Colo; Excerpt from Essay (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Catalogue - John Farris Poem (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Catalogue - Complete Text, [1989 - 1992] (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - David Hammons [1989.04]: Catalogue Orders, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Invitations, June 17, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Press Release, June 17, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Contract, October 20, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Biographical Information (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Correspondence, 1989 - 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Installation Notes (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Price List (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Public Program - Poetry Rican/Structuring, June 23, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Exhibition Checklist, June 17, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Potential Buyers (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Press Clippings, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Catalogue Essays (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Catalogue Sales (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Exhibition Travel - Fact Sheet (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Exhibition Travel - Colorado University Art Gallery, October 6 - November 11, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Exhibition Travel - Massachusetts College of Art, November 6 - December 4, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Juan Sanchez: Rican/Structured Convictions [1989.05]: Translation of Text from Paintings (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Invitations, September 23, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Press Release (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Research Materials (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Biographical Information, 1989 - 1990 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Loan Information - Centre Pompidou (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Wall Text (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Press Clippings - Exhibition, 1989 - 1991 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Press Clippings - Homeless Vehicle, 1988 - 1990 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Catalogue Text, [1989 - 1990] (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Catalogue Essays, [1990] (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Catalogue Publication Party, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Fact Sheet, January 1988, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Correspondence, 1989 - 1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Schedules, 1990 - 1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - The Painted Bride Art Center (Philadelphia), November 1 - 26, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Tyne International Exhibition, May 18 - October 21, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Oregon Art Institute, September - November 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Wexner Center for the Visual Arts (Ohio), March - April 1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, March - May 1991 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Indianapolis Museum of Art, September - November 1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Washington Project for the Arts, November 16, 1990 - January 15, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Galerie Gabrielle Maubrie (Paris), 1991 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Whitney Museum of American Art, May 19 - July 10, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Foundacion Tapies (Barcelona Olympics), June - September 1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Washington University Gallery of Art, August - November 1992 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Artex '93 (Nagoya, Japan), April 1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Krzysztof Wodiczko: New York City Tableaux [1989.06]: Exhibition Travel - Walker Art Center, October 11 - January 3, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Invitations, November 1, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Press Release, November 1, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Biographical Information, [1988 - 1990] (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Artist's Statement (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Correspondence, 1989 - 1991; 1991 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Price List, November 1, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Labels (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Public Program - "Heremeneutical Considerations of the Bishop's Moose", November 1, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Writings - "The Mystery of the Two Islands: The true story of how Cuban Communists gained control of Trump Tower" by Jose Bedia and Jimmie Durham [Manuscript], [1984, 1987] (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Writings - "The Mystery of the Two Islands: The true story of how Cuban Communists gained control of Trump Tower" by Jose Bedia and Jimmie Durham [Bound], [1984, 1987] (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Writings - "Shoot Three Hands" A Screenplay by Jimmie Durham [Manuscript], 1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Writings - Text from Installations, 1988 - 1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Writings - Miscellaneous by Jimmie Durham, [1989 - 1990] (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Press Clippings (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Travel - Schedule (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Travel - Shipping Information (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Travel - Outgoing Condition Reports, May 22, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Travel - Western Gallery (Washington), February 23 - March 23, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Travel - Center for Contemporary Arts of Santa Fe, July 19 - August 1, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Travel - Canadian Museum ov Civilization, November 1991 - January 1992 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Travel - CU Art Galleries (Colorado), February - March 1992 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Jimmie Durham [1989.07]: Exhibition Travel - Santa Barbara Contemporary Arts Forum, April 25 - June 13, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Original Proposal - Performance Art of the Soviet Union (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Research Materials - Articles by Margarita and Victor Tupitsyn, 1985, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Research Materials - Articles about Soviet Artists, 1985, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Invitations, December 9, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Press Release, December 9, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Press Kit (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Guest Curator - Margarita Tupitsyn (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Prospectus (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Budget (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Correspondence, 1988 - 1989 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Loan Information (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Exhibition Checklist, December 9, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Price List, December 9, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Installation Notes (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Exhibition Wall Text (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Press Clippings, 1989 - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Catalogue Essays (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Catalogue Inserts (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Catalogue Orders, [1989 - 1990] (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Exhibition Travel - Fact Sheet, [1989 - 1990] (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Exhibition Travel - Loan Forms, [1989 - 1990] (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Exhibition Travel - Correspondence, 1989 - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Exhibition Travel - Shipping Information, 1989 - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Exhibition Travel - Dunlap Art Gallery (Canada), October - December 1990 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - The Green Show [1989.08]: Exhibition Travel - Mendel Art Gallery (Canada), January - March 1991 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Samuel Beckett Society Membership Materials, 1989 - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Research Materials, 1989 - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Invitations, January 27, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Press Release, January 26, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Programs, January 27, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Loan Information, 1989 - 1990 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Mailing Lists, January 1, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Beckett Fan Club Listings, 1989 - 1990 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Installation / Technical Information (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Live Performances - "Catastrophe" and "Not I", January - February 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Reservations, February 1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Receipts (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Project Staff List (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: Press Clippings (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Samuel Beckett: The Media Work [1990.01]: A.F.A. Tour (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Research Materials, 1990, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Invitations, March 3, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Press Kits (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists' Statements (Box 24, Folder 15)